<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open Slice</title><link>http://example.org/docs/</link><description>Recent content on Open Slice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/about-us/</guid><description>About Us # Open Slice is a non-profit organization providing effective educational solutions to students and educators. We’re a team of like-minded people who work to eliminate roadblocks to learning.
We are a young establishment based out of Pink City consisting of hackers, developers, artists, makers and alike who believe in open education.
We run schools. We develop apps. We design curriculum. We organise hackathons. We also slay edtechs.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/donate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/donate/</guid><description>Donate : # Consider donating a few bucks. Unlike edtechs we don&amp;rsquo;t aim to make millions in profit. We&amp;rsquo;re doing this because we like teaching. And without the greed of profit, even small amounts can take us a long way ahead. Donations to Open Slice go towards our education initiatives, and help pay for services, staff and support development of digital solutions we provide.
Scan &amp;amp; Pay to support our work, Every penny counts</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/garage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/garage/</guid><description>Garage # Other than donations, you can contribute to the initiative by joining the garage. Garage consists of projects that you can work on, currently we have the following programmes running under the garage.
Open Source Program Ever wanted to work in open source ? This is your chance.
Design, develop, test and maintain codebase of our digital solutions. This includes apps, websites, community projects etc.
Whether you want to get started with open source, or gain some experience to put on your cv, this program will provide great learning opportunities.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/products/</guid><description>Products # Our products are free to use so anyone can leverage them, pay what you like or don&amp;rsquo;t. The idea is to basically crowd fund products for educators and students that are truely open. Free to use, open sourced without any caveats : no ad walls, no data mining etc.
Question Bank Question Bank provides personalised question papers. You start by taking a test.
Based on the test scores the app infers what topics you need to work on, which it reflects on the question set next time you take a test.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/services/</guid><description>Services # We do sell our services, and raise funds. These go towards our education initiatives, and help pay for servers, services, and staff.
Deep Blue Lorem markdownum insigne. Olympo signis Delphis! Retexi Nereius nova develat stringit, frustra Saturnius uteroque inter ! Oculis non ritibus Telethusa
Expand shortcode can help to decrease clutter on screen by hiding part of text. Expand content by clicking on it.Expand shortcode can help to decrease clutter on screen by hiding part of text.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/docs/thanks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/thanks/</guid><description>Thanks for your support ! # I would like to express my deep gratitude to Professor and Professor , my research supervisors, for their patient guidance, enthusiastic encouragement and useful critiques of this research work. I would also like to thank Dr, for her advice and assistance in keeping my progress on schedule.
I would also like to extend my thanks to the technicians of the laboratory of the department for their help in offering me the resources in running the program.</description></item></channel></rss>